<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
 <TIPS>
     <TIP>
        <CATEGORY>Dress/Alterations</CATEGORY>
		<TITLE>Buy a second hand prom dress</TITLE>
        <CONTENT>Usually, prom dresses are worn for one night only. There are many organizations that sell used but practically brand new prom dresses for a cheaper cost. Also, check out consignment shops where you might find a vintage dress that will showcase your personality.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
         <CATEGORY>Dress/Alterations</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Raid family closets</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Chances are, your older brother, cousin, or, yes, even your dad, have a tux you can borrow – for free! Go shopping in their closets to see if their style fits yours.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
         <CATEGORY>Dress/Alterations</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Visit discount clothing stores</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Prom dresses don’t have a very long shelf life. Instead of visiting a high-end fashion store, find a similar outfit at discount clothing stores.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
         <CATEGORY>Dress/Alterations</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Design your own dress</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Inspired by Project Runway? If you’re particularly creative and good with a needle, show off your talents by making your own dress.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
	<TIP>
	    <CATEGORY>Shoes</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Buy shoes online</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Many websites such as Zappos often carry designer shoes for less than the price you’d find in stores.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
         <CATEGORY>Accessories</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Rent dresses or accessories</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Companies like Rent the Runway allow you to rent dresses and jewelry for special occasions. By renting the dress for a night, you can save yourself the trouble of buying a dress for one-time use.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
         <CATEGORY>Hair</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Do your own hair and nails</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Invite your best friends over the morning of the prom, relax, throw on some music, and save money by fixing each other’s hair and painting your nails. You’ll be glad you spent more time with your friends, and spent less money.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
	<TIP>
     	<CATEGORY>Tickets</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Buy your tickets early.</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Some schools offer discounted tickets for students that buy them in advance. Be sure to buy your tickets as early as possible.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
		<CATEGORY>Boutonniere</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Make your own boutonniere</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Visit your local grocery store and buy small/midsize flowers such as roses or carnations. With ribbon and wire, you can create your own unique boutonniere that your date will be proud to show off.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
         <CATEGORY>Dinner</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Find restaurants with special prom menus</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Many restaurants offer special menus targeting prom couples. Look for restaurants that offer discounted rates for multi-course prom dinners.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
     	<CATEGORY>Transportation</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Borrow a family car</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Instead of shelling out hundreds of dollars to rent a limo, ask your parents, brother, uncle, or anyone with a cool car to loan you theirs for the night. Offer to clean it for free and fill it with gas in return.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
      <TIP>
         <CATEGORY>Transportation</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Divide and conquer.</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Buy splitting the costs of a limo or bus with several of your friends, you drive your own personal costs down.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
     	<CATEGORY>Pictures</CATEGORY>
         <TITLE>Stay smart</TITLE>
         <CONTENT>Smart phones have great cameras and plenty of sharing options. Save yourself some money by taking your own pictures.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
     	<CATEGORY>After Party</CATEGORY>
        <TITLE>Stay in school</TITLE>
        <CONTENT>Many schools offer cheap, “official” after parties. Convince your friends to save money by going to the school after party. As long as you’re together, any party will be fun.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
     <TIP>
     	<CATEGORY>After Party</CATEGORY>
        <TITLE>Head home</TITLE>
        <CONTENT>Have a small gathering at home with your closest friends.</CONTENT>
     </TIP>
 </TIPS>
